

PROFILE

9 years of web developing experience for multiple domains including business, healthcare, e-commerce, etc.

Blockchain developer with 4 years of experience for Dapps, NFT, Web3 projects etc.

Excellent smart contract coding ability and skilled in developing blockchain projects using Hardhat, Remix, ether.js and web3.js.

LINK

website

CONTACT

Address:

1132 Granada Street, Fort Pierce, Florida, United States

PHONE: (805) 214-8119

EMAIL:

phillipgrandi89@gmail.com

LANGUGAE

English

HOBBIES

Football Piano

PHILLIP GRANDINETTI

Blockchain Developer 4 years Full Stack Engineer 7 years Web Developer 9 years

EDUCATION

University of Virginia

August 2008 – May 2013

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

WORK EXPERIENCE

Modea (Junior Web Developer)

May 2013 – October 2015

Developed healthcare web application frontends using React.js, Redux and Vue.js.

Kortek Solutions (Full Stack Developer)

October 2015 - July 2018

Kortek Solutions provides small and medium-sized business with a range of services and solutions. I have developed several projects using React.is, Vue.is and Node.is as business service.

SoluLab (Blockchain Developer)

July 2018 - February 2020

Developed smart contracts with Solidity using Remix and Hardhat to deploy on several blockchain networks Created and deployed ERC20, ERC721 tokens to blockchain networks

Chainalysis Inc (Full Stack Developer)

February 2020 - July 2022

Built frontend and backend for Web3 projects based on ethereum network using React.js, Redux, Vue.js, Web3.js and Ether.js according to requirements and development guidelines

SKILLS

